[{"answer": "Good to hear it.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "You know, actually I don't think so.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "He's a bit of a problem for you, isn't he?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, again, we've got to get out of political cliches.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "If the American public just basically don't want to pay more tax, aren't they going to lean in an election in economic hard times towards the party that is saying, I'm not going to hit you in the pocket so hard?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Piers, this is really what I recoil about in where our politics is getting now and is being fueled by super PAC money, is being fueled by a media that becomes so much more obsessed with sound bites than substance.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Well, I think that I've been clear on the record about my feelings about these super PACs and the negativity on both sides.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "I mean does your anger extend to that kind of stuff?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "So, Piers, two points.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "When you take all these things into consideration, you must be disappointed that the president isn't ordering some new form of gun control, aren't you?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "You're very nice to me.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Hi, Piers, how are you?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "IULIANI: Well, what about -- what about -- I have no idea.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Had he said shackles rather than chains, had he said that, would it have made any difference to you?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "No, no, I wasn't -- I wasn't shocked or dismayed.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "How would you describe your honest reaction?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I think that Governor Romney has made a gamble here.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "-- and the public don't buy into him at the election, that's a problem, isn't it?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Sure, if you want.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "To Grover, you're obviously now into pre-election mode which I would imagine means you're going to be even more aggressive about this than normal, right?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Well, the best attack line for the Democrats is just looking at the details of the plan.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "So Michael Linden, from your point of view, where is the best attack line for the Democrats?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Well, there are two things.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "What do you do about that?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "What Obama did is he's just changed the rules.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "What do you want to say?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "ATHER: Well, I think it's gotten worse.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "What do you make of the way they are all going at each other now?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "He's definitely resonating with the American public.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "It would be very interesting to see how well the Republicans do at their convention in changing the conversation back to do you agree with Obama or not Obama, rather than do you agree with Paul Ryan and his plan or not?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "It would be ironic.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "And it would be truly ironic if it was that that cost Mitt Romney the election, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I'm not surprised because people always have something to say.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Are you surprised by it?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Well, you make this sound so --", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "So what was harder, \"Dancing With the Stars\", that or getting in a ring pounding somebody away as the try to beat you up?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Anyway, they're all different.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Real?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "The best thing, just off the top of my head, is just knowing that I have that same blood running through my veins.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "What is the best and worst thing about being Mohammed Ali's daughter?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "120815pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Actually, it's been great to meet you because you're a chip off the old block really, aren't you?", "qSentId": 538}]